# SUHAIL OSMAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **PROFILE**

Web Developer with experince in designing and developing and testing, debuging create, code and maintain server-side technologies, that are used to store and access data by website or through an app. they worked closely with front-end developer

## CONTACT



#### Address:

9, Mahas Street Khartoum, Aljreef Sudan



## Phones:

+249-117-404015 (mobile) +249 -92395210 (mobile)



# e-mail:

sahlowle@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

- + PHP/LARAVEL
- + HTML/CSS
- + ANGULAR
- + Photoshop

#### LANGUAGES

- + Arabic
- + English

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

SkilledTech , UAE (2019- Present)

# Web Developer,

back-end developer create api using laravel framework, front-end developer using angular framework.

Ministry of Defense, SD (2018-2019)

#### Web Developer,

web designer using bootstarp framework, backend-developer using php pure and custom libaray

Ashrafcom, SD (3 months)

# Web Developer,

backend developer create api by using django python framework.

(2013-2017)

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelors Degree**

" First Degree ".

Sudan University of Since & Technology Management Information System Department.

# REFERENCES

#### MONZER OSMAN.

CEO at SkilledTech. **P.** 00249-913513235

E. skilledtech2019@gmail.com



